Guide to the Gitel P. Steed Papers 1907-1980
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: The Columbia University Research in Contemporary India Field Project
  - Subseries 2: Seminar on Rural India
    - Lecture 22, Rorschach case histories, April 1, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Lecture 23, Child-rearing, April 8, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Lecture 23, Child-rearing, April 8, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Caste, notes from lectures, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Caste, notes from lectures, field notes, 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Informant 2, conference with Dr. Kardiner, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Some facts about the data," memorandum to Dr. Kardiner, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Urban Life Histories and Tests
    - United States, Rorschach, Thematic Apperception Test (TAT), Horn-Hellersburg (H-H), 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - India, Rorschach, informant list, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bombay, Rorschach, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Bombay, Rorschach, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Bombay, TAT, correspondence, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Bombay, H-H, Child Development Test, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Bombay, Child Development Test, December 22, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Ahmedabad, Informant 1, January 18-June 2, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Ahmedabad, Informant 1, January 18-June 2, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Ahmedabad, Informant 2, April 10-May 1, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Ahmedabad, Informants 3-6, unidentified, H-H, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Ahmedabad, Brahmin Informant, notes, May 23-June 28, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Ahmedabad, Rorschach, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Ahmedabad, TAT, May-June, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Ahmedabad, H-H, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Ahmedabad, H-H, 1950. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Uttar Pradesh, Rorschach, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Uttar Pradesh, Rorschach, rural sample, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Uttar Pradesh, Rorschach, H-H, Delhi, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Uttar Pradesh, TAT, H-H, Draw-a-man, urban and rural, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Uttar Pradesh, TAT, H-H, Draw-a-man, urban and rural, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Uttar Pradesh, Draw-a-man, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Uttar Pradesh, Draw-a-man, Color Association Test, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Punjab, Rorschach, H-H, Draw-a-man, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Udaipur, H-H, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Madras, H-H, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 4: Notecards
    - Field data analysis, 1950 (Box 9)
    - Field data analysis, 1950 (Box 10)
    - Reading research notes, undated (Box 11)
- Series III: Kasandra, 1950
  This series contains all of the research materials produced from the study of Kasandra, a village in Gujarat State. These files were divided into eighteen subseries.
  Subseries 1, Informant Life Histories and Psychodiagnostic Tests, contains life history material for 25 informants and includes a personal narration as well as a set of psychodiagnostic tests. The personal narration consists of typed transcriptions of interviews that took place in some cases over the course of an entire year. Informants were asked to speak and reflect as freely as possible on the things that they felt affected their life as they grew up and interacted with others. The psychodiagnostic tests include one or more of the following: Rorschach (which asks informants to identify shapes in ink blots), Thematic Apperception Test (which informants are shown a series of illustrations and asked to talk about the situation, people in it, what they might be doing, thinking, or feeling), Horn-Hellersberg (a drawing test), Draw-a-man (which informants are asked to draw and comment on a man, woman and child), and Color Association Test (designed for India, where informants are given a set of words and asked to
  associate a color with the idea conveyed by the words). The amount of data varies for each informant.
  Subseries 2, Psychodiagnostic Tests, contains the results of all tests categorized not by informant but by the test type. The tests were administered to more informants than were asked to give personal narration's.
  Subseries 3 and 4, General Notes, contain notes by Gitel Steed and James Silverberg, respectively. These are typed transcripts from field notebooks that contain daily observations of life and work in Kasandra and have been chronologically arranged.
  Subseries 5, Census Data, contains data of the village, including economic information categorized by household and caste. A set of maps of Kasandra is also included. Some of these maps are smaller versions of those found in Series II, subseries 5.
  Subseries 6, Indices, contains a set of indices that Steed and her team devised in order to locate data on certain topics within their notes. Indices for demography, caste, politics, economics, religion, child behavior, and social relations are included. These indices reference the dates and page numbers of data to be found in general notes, life histories, and psychodiagnostic tests.
  Subseries 7 through 13 are topical. Government, Politics, and Rajputs; Caste and Kinship; Economics; Land Tenure; Land Utilization Survey; Structure of Family and Child Life; and Religion. These subseries include maps, charts, genealogies, survey results, copies of government surveys and reports, a few manuscripts on the specified topics, and many extracted notes. The extracted notes are for the most part cut-and-pasted portions taken from general notes and life histories.
  Subseries 14 through 16, Field Notebooks, were kept by Steed, Silverberg, and others, respectively. These are the notebooks that the researchers carried with them to their interviews and on their daily rounds in the village. Most of the notebooks were later typed up and their entries can be found in other places in the collection. It is not always clear which ones have been typed and which ones have not. Aside from the two main researchers, Steed and Silverberg, others also kept notebooks, including both Indian and non-Indian research assistants as well as informants themselves. An account book kept by Robert Steed is also found here. The notebooks are arranged chronologically, and headings correspond to those found on the notebooks themselves.
  Subseries 17, Drawings, contains a large number of watercolors and drawings, in pencil, pen, and charcoal, by informants of all ages. Informants drew people, animals, houses, and landscapes as well as other objects of everyday life.
  Subseries 18, Interviews, 1970-1971, contains a set of interviews Steed conducted on a return visit to India in 1970-1971. Accompanied by her husband, Steed conducted several interviews, some with her previous informants, to evaluate perceptions of social change in the intervening twenty years.
  - Subseries 1: Informant Life Histories and Psychodiagnostic Tests
    - List of informants (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - List of informants (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Informant lists for drawings and tests (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Informant lists for drawings and tests (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Informants 1-3, 8-10, indexes to political and economic data (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Informant 1, personal narration (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Informant 1, personal narration (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Informant 1, personal narration (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Informant 1, Rorschach, Thematic Apperception Test (TAT), Horn-Hellersberg (H-H), Draw-a-man, Color Association, provisional color association word list, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Informant 1, test interviews (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Informant 1, Rorschach, analysis by Alice Cottingham, undated (2) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Informant 1, Rorschach, analysis by Alice Cottingham, undated (2) (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Informant 1, H-H (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Informant 1, H-H, analysis by Elisabeth Hellersberg, correspondence, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Informant 1, Draw-a-man (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Informant 1, word lists, index (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Informant 1, general notes, extracts on religion (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Informant 2, personal narration, word list, inventory, indexes (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Informant 2, personal narration, word list, inventory, indexes (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Informant 2, personal narration, word list, inventory, indexes (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Informant 2, personal narration, word list, inventory, indexes (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Informant 2, Rorschach, TAT, H-H, Draw-a-man, Color Association, word list (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Informant 2, Rorschach, analysis by Alice Cottingham, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Informant 2, Rorschach, analysis by Dr. Goldfarb, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Informant 2, TAT (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Informant 2, TAT, analysis by E.D.K. (sic), undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Informant 2, H-H, analyses by E. Hellersberg and Gitel Steed, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Informant 2, general notes, extracts (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Informant 2, general notes, index to sociological documents (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Informant 3, personal narration (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Informant 3, personal narration (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Informant 3, personal narration (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Informant 3, personal narration (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Informant 3, index (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Informant 3, Rorschach, H-H, Draw-a-man, Color Association (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Informant 3, test interviews (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Informant 3, test interviews (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Informant 3, word lists (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Informant 3, indexes (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Informant 4, personal narration (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Informant 4, personal narration (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Informant 4, personal narration, extracts undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Informant 4, Rorschach (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Informant 4, Rorschach, analysis by Alice Cottingham, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Informant 5, personal narration (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Informant 5, Rorschach (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Informant 5, TAT. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Informant 5, H-H. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Informant 6, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Informant 6, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Informant 6, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Informant 6, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Informant 6, personal narration, extracts, kinship chart. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Informant 7, personal narration, errata notes. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Informant 7, personal narration, errata notes. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Informant 7, Rorschach, analysis. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Informant 7, Rorschach, analysis. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Informant 7, Rorschach, analysis by Alice Cottingham, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Informant 7, lecture 20 extract, 1950, 1953. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Informant 8, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Informant 8, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Informant 8, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Informant 8, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Informant 8, personal narration (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Informant 9, personal narration (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Informant 9, personal narration (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Informant 9, personal narration (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Informant 9, word list, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Informant 10, personal narration (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Informant 10, personal narration (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Informant 10, personal narration (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Informant 10, Rorschach, TAT, H-H, Draw-a-man, Color Association (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Informant 10, test interviews (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Informant 10, word lists (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Informant 12, personal narration (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Informant 12, Rorschach (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Informants 12, 19, 23, 25, personal narrations, extracts, Thakur genealogy (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Informant 13, personal narration, note cards (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Informant 13, Rorschach (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Informant 14, personal narration (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Informant 14, Rorschach (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Informant 15, personal narration (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Informant 15, Rorschach, TAT, H-H, James Silverberg notes (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Informant 15, Rorschach, TAT, H-H, James Silverberg notes (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Informant 15, extracts from James Silverberg notes (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Informant 15, Lebensraum, extracts (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Informant 15, extracts (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Informant 15, general notes, extracts, kinship chart, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Informant 15, James Silverberg general notes (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Informant 15, James Silverberg general notes (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Informant 18, personal narration (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Informant 19, personal narration (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Informant 15 Rorschach (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Informant 20, personal narration (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Informant 22, personal narration (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Informant 23, personal narration (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Informant 25, personal narration (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Informant 26, personal narration, general notes, land-use survey, account book (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Informant 26, personal narration, general notes, land-use survey, account book (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Informant 26, personal narration, Rorschach, general notes, index (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Informant 26, general notes, index (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Informant 30, personal narration, H-H. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Informant 31, personal narration, James Silverberg general notes, extracts (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Informant 32, personal narration (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Informant 33, personal narration (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Informant 33, Rorschach (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2: Psychodiagnostic Tests
    - Informant lists, indexes to general notes (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Total number tested by age, gender, caste (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Rorschach, list of informants (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Rorschach, Informant 21 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Rorschach, Informant 39 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Rorschach, Informant 40 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Rorschach, Informant 52 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Rorschach, Informant 81 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Rorschach, Informant 115 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Rorschach, Informant 130 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Rorschach, Informant 156 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Rorschach, Informant 158 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Rorschach, Koli-Patel informants (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Rorschach, test materials (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Rorschach, test materials (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - TAT, interviews (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - H-H, informant list (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - H-H, test materials (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - H-H, test materials (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - H-H, test materials (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - H-H, test materials (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - H-H, test materials (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - H-H, interviews (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - H-H, interviews (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - H-H, interviews (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Draw-a-man, informant list, drawings (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Draw-a-man, original drawings (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Draw-a-man, original drawings (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Draw-a-man, interviews (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Color Association Test, color key, word lists, Chinese test, colors of castes and of god, village statistics by age and gender, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Color Association Test, color key, word lists, Chinese test, colors of castes and of god, village statistics by age and gender, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Child Development Test, Informant 175, 1950, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 3: General Notes, Gitel P. Steed
    - Extracts (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Extracts (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Extracts (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Extracts (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence from Kasandra, dream, songs, cinema narration, costume, notes (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - January 28-February 5 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - February 6-16 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - February 16-28 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Extracts, October 21-December 30 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - January 28-31 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - January 28-31 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - February 1-9 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - February 1-9 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - February 11-28 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - February 11-28 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - February 1-March 15 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - February 1-March 15 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - March 1-20 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - April 1-20 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - May 6-9, diary index (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - July 18-31 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - August 1-31 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - October 21-30 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - November 4-30 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - December 1-30 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - December 1-30 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 4: General Notes, James Silverberg
    - Index, James Silverberg and Gitel P. Steed conference notes (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Index, caste (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Index, religion (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Index, economics (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Index, social, infants and children (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - January 20-March 4 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - January 20-March 4 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - January 20-March 4 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - January 20-March 4 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - January 28-31 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - January 28-February 11 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - February 12-22 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - February 23-March 8 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - March 5-30 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - March 5-30 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - March 5-30 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - April 1-23 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - April 1-23 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - April 1-23 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - April 1-23 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - June 22-30 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - July 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - July 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - July 6-31 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - July 6-31 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - July 6-31 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - July 11-15. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - October 20-November 17 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - October 20-November 17 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - October 20-November 17 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - November 1-10 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - November 11-20 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - November 18-December 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - November 18-December 3 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Kolis, intellectual and ideological roles, manuscript, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Kolis, intellectual and ideological roles, manuscript, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Kolis, production roles, manuscript, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Kolis, proprietary roles, manuscript, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Kolis, exchange roles, service roles, manuscripts, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Suthars (Carpenters), 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Kumbhars (Potters), 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 5: Census Data
    - Caste and household, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Caste and household, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Caste and household, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Caste and household, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Caste and household, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Caste and household heads, Census of India Paper No. 2, reprint, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Classified Index, Mortality statistics, 1949-1953 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Maps (Nos. 1, 5-12, 14-15), Rajput rankings, charts, 1907-1960. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 6: Indices
    - Original indexing categories (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Chronological index to GPS general (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Classified, One (The Physical Village), Two (Social Structure in Transition), 1948-1951 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Classified, Two, demography (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Classified, Two, political power (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Classified, Two, political power (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Classified, Two, religion and ritual, rural economics, "Structure of Child Behavior," outlines (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Classified, political, economic, social (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Classified, Informant 3 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Social (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Caste (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Children (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Property, extracts, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 7: Government, Politics, and Rajputs
    - Imperial Gazetteer of India, classified index, history of Rajputs, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Imperial Gazetteer of India, classified index, extracts, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Imperial Gazetteer of India, extracts, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, newspaper clippings, 1949-50 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - The village as an area of inquiry, notes, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Kinship, land tenure, agriculture (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Maps, informant map (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Vaghela Rajputs, history, genealogy, research notes, kinship charts, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Vaghela Rajputs, political power, genealogy, research notes, lecture excerpt, 1950-1953 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Vaghela Rajputs, as Darbars, village administration, gazetteer notes, research notes, kinship chart, lecture extract, 1950-1953 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Vaghela Rajputs, local administration and village Talukdari powers, interview notes, history, notecards, November 23, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Vaghela Rajputs, leadership and status, Informant 1, interview, November 23, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Vaghela Rajputs, Purdah households, child health survey, color association test, research notes, March-April, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Vaghela Rajputs, Moti-deli, structure of family life, research notes, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Jhala-Rajputs, Informant 3, interview, genealogy, Police Sub-Inspector's Office "Visitors Book" (1942-1950) (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Koli-Patels, analysis of kinship system, lineages, notes, kinship charts, kinship terms (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Koli-Patels, analysis of kinship system, lineages, notes, kinship charts, kinship terms (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Harijans, General Notes, extracts, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Culture change in the village, notes, November, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Subseries 8: Caste and Kinship
    - Caste, kinship practices (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Caste hierarchy, ritual calender (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Religion, varna, seating arrangements, Hindu compared to Muslim, Jains, 1950, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Caste lists, Bakrana compared against M. N. Srinivas list of castes, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Color associations, dress, restrictions, manuscript, notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Silverberg, James, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Brahmin and other kinship terms, marriage networks (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Rajputs, village endogamy, extracts (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Vaghela-Rajputs, wedding, correspondence (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Vaghela-Rajputs, political power, Imperial Gazetteer extracts, correspondence, manuscript (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Vaghela-Rajputs, Moti-deli, Nani-deli, manuscripts, historical chart, kinship chart, note cards, 1950-1953 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Vaghela-Rajputs, kinship chart (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Jhala-Rajputs, Motawanta, Nanawanta, general notes, extracts (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Jhala-Rajputs, and others, kinship system (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Jhala-Rajputs, marriage practices, research notes, charts (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Jhala-Rajputs, Informant 3, genealogical chart (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Banyas, Informant 22 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Banyas, Jainism, indexes, kinship notes, house plan, note cards. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Kolis, James Silverberg interviews with A. R. Desai and D. N. Majumdar, September, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 19)